Guide to the Records of the Grey Art Gallery and Study Center RG.42.5
New York University Archives
- Series II: Administrative Files, 1961-1988; 212471
  - Subseries D: Development, 1964-1980; 212472
    - Goldin, Nan, 1982 September-1983 January; 213162 (Box II:4, Folder 11)
    - Heister, Scott, 1982 September-1983 January; 213161 (Box II:4, Folder 12)
    - Hockney, David, 1982 October-1984 April; 213160 (Box II:4, Folder 13)
    - Hujar, Peter, 1982 September-1983 January; 213159 (Box II:4, Folder 14)
    - McGowan, Kenneth, 1982 January-November; 213158 (Box II:4, Folder 15)
    - Ricatto, Cosimo Di Leo, 1982 September-1983 January; 213157 (Box II:4, Folder 16)
    - Seidner, David, 1982 September-1983 October; 213156 (Box II:4, Folder 17)
    - Sherman, Cindy, 1982 September-1983 January; 213155 (Box II:4, Folder 18)
    - Springs, Alice, 1982 January-1983 January; 213154 (Box II:4, Folder 19)
    - Weber, Bruce, 1982 September-1983 January; 213153 (Box II:4, Folder 20)
    - Winokur, Neil, 1982 September-1983 January; 213152 (Box II:4, Folder 21)
    - Wegman, William, 1982 October-1983 February; 213151 (Box II:4, Folder 22)
    - Faces Photographed, 1982 October; 213150 (Box II:4, Folder 23)
    - Turkish Exhibition -- AXIA, 1982 October-1983 December; 213149 (Box II:4, Folder 24)
    - Turkish Loans, Transportation, Insurance, etc., 1982 October-1983 July; 213148 (Box II:4, Folder 25)
    - Turkish Exhibitions -- Additional Loans, 1983 January-July; 213147 (Box II:4, Folder 26)
    - Kahlo/Modotti Funding, 1982 March-1983 July; 213146 (Box II:4, Folder 27)
    - Kohlo/Modotti Pending Lenders, 1982 July-1983 April; 213145 (Box II:4, Folder 28)
    - Francis Returns (Kahlo/Modotti), 1983 April; 213144 (Box II:4, Folder 29)
    - Pandolfi Returns (Kahlo/Modotti), 1983; 213143 (Box II:4, Folder 30)
    - Kahlo -- Additional Loans Responses (1 of 2), 1981 December-1987 May; 213142 (Box II:4, Folder 31)
    - Kahlo -- Additional Loans Responses (2 of 2), 1981 December-1987 May; 213141 (Box II:4, Folder 32)
    - Kahlo/Modotti -- 1982 NEA Grant, 213140 (Box II:4, Folder 33)
    - Kahlo/Modotti -- Transportation and Insurance, 1983 January-May; 213139 (Box II:4, Folder 34)
    - Two Installations - Correspondence, 1982 April-November; 213138 (Box II:4, Folder 35)
    - Elgort, Arthur, 1983 January 12; 213137 (Box II:4, Folder 36)
    - Outerbridge -- Insurance, 1983 September-October; 213136 (Box II:4, Folder 37)
    - Paul Outerbridge -- Transportation, 1983 September-October; 213135 (Box II:4, Folder 38)
    - Outerbridge -- Release Letters of 2 Prints, 1983 October; 213134 (Box II:4, Folder 39)
    - Outerbridge -- Condition Report, 1983 July-October; 213133 (Box II:4, Folder 40)
    - Paul Outerbridge -- Correspondence, 1982 May-1984 April; 213132 (Box II:4, Folder 41)
    - Condition Reports, 1982 August-1985 March; 213131 (Box II:4, Folder 42)
    - Eva Hesse Drawings -- 1983, 1980 October-1983 February; 213130 (Box II:4, Folder 43)
    - Eva Hesse -- Additional Sculpture, 1982 October-1983 July; 213129 (Box II:4, Folder 44)
    - Bergdorf/Montana -- Correspondence, 1983 February-July; 213128 (Box II:4, Folder 45)
    - Louis Dahl-Wolfe -- Loan Form, 1983 September; 213127 (Box II:4, Folder 46)
    - Picasso -- Loans Rejected, 1983 June 10; 213126 (Box II:4, Folder 47)
    - Picasso -- Funding, 1982 February-1984 March; 213125 (Box II:4, Folder 48)
    - Picasso -- NEA Grant, 1982 July-1984 January; 213124 (Box II:4, Folder 49)
    - Picasso -- Correspondence with Schiff, 1982 July-1983 April; 213123 (Box II:4, Folder 50)
    - Picasso -- Correspondence, 1982 July-1984 February; 213122 (Box II:4, Folder 51)
    - Picasso -- Guggenheim, 1983 December-1984 January; 213121 (Box II:4, Folder 52)
    - Picasso -- Japan, 1983 August-November; 213120 (Box II:4, Folder 53)
    - Picasso -- Braziller Contract, 1983 August-1984 August; 213119 (Box II:4, Folder 54)
    - Picasso -- Budget, 1983 October 27; 213118 (Box II:4, Folder 55)
    - Picasso -- Insurance and Shipping, 1983 January-December; 213117 (Box II:4, Folder 56)
    - Picasso -- Japan (Loans Rejected), 1983 August-October; 213116 (Box II:4, Folder 57)
    - Picasso -- Photograph Permission for Catalogue, 1983 July-December; 213115 (Box II:4, Folder 58)
    - Picasso -- Financial, 1983 September-1984 February; 213114 (Box II:4, Folder 59)
    - Picasso -- Loans Pending, 1982 October-1983 July; 213113 (Box II:4, Folder 60)
    - Picasso -- Photographs, 1983 June-1984 November; 213112 (Box II:4, Folder 61)
    - Picasso -- Pace Editions, Inc. and Pace Gallery, 1983 July-September; 213111 (Box II:5, Folder 1)
    - Picasso -- Paloma, 1983 August-October; 213110 (Box II:5, Folder 2)
    - Artvest Associates/Co. Veron, Grauer (See Paloma Picasso), 1983 October; 213109 (Box II:5, Folder 3)
    - Musee Picasso, 1984 August-December; 213108 (Box II:5, Folder 4)
    - Picasso -- Reiss-Cohen, Inc., 1983 July-September; 213107 (Box II:5, Folder 5)
    - Picasso -- Galerie Rosengart, 1982 October-1984 January; 213106 (Box II:5, Folder 6)
    - Picasso -- Marcel Ebnother (Via Rosengart), Circa 1983-1984; 213105 (Box II:5, Folder 7)
    - Picasso -- Saidenberg, 1983 September; 213104 (Box II:5, Folder 8)
    - Picasso -- Sindin Galleries, 1983 September; 213103 (Box II:5, Folder 9)
    - Picasso -- Javier Vilato, 1983 May-November; 213102 (Box II:5, Folder 10)
    - Picasso -- William Acquavella, 1982 November-1983 September; 213101 (Box II:5, Folder 11)
    - Picasso -- Albright-Knox Art Gallery, 1982 October-1983 September; 213100 (Box II:5, Folder 12)
    - Picasso -- Thomas Amman Fine Arts, 1983 July-September; 213099 (Box II:5, Folder 13)
    - Picasso -- Gilbert de Bottom (Thomas Ammann), 1983 October; 213098 (Box II:5, Folder 14)
    - Picasso -- Brigitte Baer (Widmaier Loans), 1982 December-1983 September; 213097 (Box II:5, Folder 15)
    - Picasso -- Galerie Beyeler, 1982 November-1983 September; 213096 (Box II:5, Folder 16)
    - Picasso -- Evelym Blum, 1982 October-1983 October; 213095 (Box II:5, Folder 17)
    - Picasso -- Fuji Television Gallery Co. Ltd, 1983 August-1985 January; 213094 (Box II:5, Folder 18)
    - Picasso -- Museum of Fine Arts (Boston), 1983 May-November; 213093 (Box II:5, Folder 19)
    - Picasso -- Aldis Browne, 1983 September; 213092 (Box II:5, Folder 20)
    - Picasso -- Morton Janklow, 1982 November-1983 December; 213091 (Box II:5, Folder 21)
    - Picasso -- David Hockney, 1983 September; 213090 (Box II:5, Folder 22)
    - Picasso -- Kunsthaus Zurich, 1983 September-December; 213089 (Box II:5, Folder 23)
    - Picasso -- Donald Marron, 1983 September; 213088 (Box II:5, Folder 24)
    - Picasso -- Metropolitan Museum of Art, 1983 July-December; 213087 (Box II:5, Folder 25)
    - Picasso -- Owen Morrissey, 1982 November-1983 September; 213086 (Box II:5, Folder 26)
    - Picasso -- Raymond Nasher, 1982 November-1983 September; 213085 (Box II:5, Folder 27)
    - Picasso -- Galerie Louise Leiris (1 of 2), 1982 December-1984 September; 213084 (Box II:5, Folder 28)
    - Picasso -- Galerie Louise Leiris (2 of 2), 1982 December-1984 September; 213083 (Box II:5, Folder 29)
    - Picasso -- Louvre, 1983 July-September; 213082 (Box II:5, Folder 30)
    - Picasso -- Reproductions, 1983 September; 213081 (Box II:5, Folder 31)
    - Picasso -- Galeries Van Krugier, 1983 September-November; 213080 (Box II:5, Folder 32)
    - Bay Area Painting -- Paul Wonner (Pending), 1983 June-September; 213079 (Box II:5, Folder 33)
    - Bay Area Painting -- Paul Wonner (Confirmed), 1983 September-1984 November; 213078 (Box II:5, Folder 34)
    - Bay Area Painting -- Paul Wonner (Rejections), 1983 September-1984 January; 213077 (Box II:5, Folder 35)
    - Bay Area Painting -- Insurance, 1983 August -- 1984 June; 213076 (Box II:5, Folder 36)
    - Bay Area Painting -- Financial, 1983 October-1984 May; 213075 (Box II:5, Folder 37)
    - Bay Area Painting -- Crating Bills, 1983 March-1984 June; 213074 (Box II:5, Folder 38)
    - Bay Area Painting -- Park Requests, 1983 August-1984 January; 213073 (Box II:5, Folder 39)
    - Bay Area Painting -- Park Rejected, 1983 September-November; 213072 (Box II:5, Folder 40)
    - Bay Area Painting -- Park Confirmed, 1983 May-1984 December; 213071 (Box II:5, Folder 41)
    - Bay Area Painting -- Bob's File, 1984 February-March; 213070 (Box II:5, Folder 42)
    - Bay Area Painting -- Correspondence to Newport Harbor, 1984 July; 213069 (Box II:5, Folder 43)
    - Bay Area Painting -- North California Figs., 1981 December-1984 April; 213068 (Box II:5, Folder 44)
    - Bay Area Painting -- North California Figs. (Newport Harbor), 1982 August-1984 February; 213067 (Box II:5, Folder 45)
    - Bay Area Painting -- North California Figs. (Rejections for Newport Harbor), 1983 September-1984 February; 213066 (Box II:5, Folder 46)
    - Bay Area Painting -- North California Figs. (Joan Brown), 1984 March-April; 213065 (Box II:5, Folder 47)
    - Bay Area Painting -- North California (Bischoff Rejected), 1983 September; 213064 (Box II:5, Folder 48)
    - Bay Area Painting -- North California (Bischoff Pending), 1983 June-December; 213063 (Box II:5, Folder 49)
    - Bay Area Painting -- North California (Diebenkorn Loans Confirmed), 1983 May-1984 December; 213062 (Box II:5, Folder 50)
    - Bay Area Painting -- North California (Diebenkorn Pending), Circa 1982-1984; 213061 (Box II:5, Folder 51)
    - Bay Area Painting -- North California, 1983 May-November; 213060 (Box II:5, Folder 52)
    - Bay Area Painting -- North California - Bischoff Loans Confirmed, 1983 March-1984 December; 213059 (Box II:5, Folder 53)
    - Bay Area Painting -- Photo Bills, 1983 June-1985 January; 213058 (Box II:5, Folder 54)
    - Bay Area Painting --Invoices, 1983 October-1984 June; 213057 (Box II:5, Folder 55)
    - Bay Area Painting --Oliveira Pending, 1983 June-1984 March; 213056 (Box II:5, Folder 56)
    - Bay Area Painting --Northern California Figs. (Nathan Oliveira), 1983 June-1984 February; 213055 (Box II:5, Folder 57)
    - Bay Area Exhibit -- Purchase Orders and Requests for Checks (1 of 2), 1984 February-September; 213054 (Box II:5, Folder 58)
    - Bay Area Exhibit -- Purchase Orders and Requests for Checks (2 of 2), 1984 February-September; 213053 (Box II:5, Folder 59)
    - Bay Area -- Cost Sharing, 1984 February-May; 213052 (Box II:5, Folder 60)
    - Bay Area Painting -- Northern California Figs. (Multiple Lenders), 1983 August-1984 December; 213051 (Box II:5, Folder 61)
    - Bay Area -- Project Budget, 1984; 213050 (Box II:5, Folder 62)
    - Bay Area Painting -- Shipping Arrangements, 1984 February-September; 213049 (Box II:5, Folder 63)
    - Bay Area Painting -- Dispersal, 1984 March-August; 213048 (Box II:5, Folder 64)
    - Bay Area Painting -- Condition Reports and Loan Receipts, 1984 January-October; 213047 (Box II:5, Folder 65)
    - Bay Area Painting -- Newport and GAG Contract, 1984 February-March; 213046 (Box II:5, Folder 66)
    - Bay Area Painting - The Figurative Mode (March 27-April 28), 1984 February-May; 213045 (Box II:5, Folder 67)
    - Cocteau -- Correspondence, 1984 June 6-7; 213044 (Box II:5, Folder 68)
    - Cocteau -- to Miami/Return of Works not Traveling, 1984 June-July; 213043 (Box II:5, Folder 69)
    - Cocteau -- Loan Fees/Crating Fees, 1984 April-August; 213042 (Box II:5, Folder 70)
    - Cocteau -- Insurance, 1984 April-June; 213041 (Box II:5, Folder 71)
    - Cocteau -- Condition Report/Loan Receipts, 1984 May-September; 213040 (Box II:5, Folder 72)
    - Cocteau -- Customs, 1984 May; 213039 (Box II:5, Folder 73)
    - Jean Cocteau -- Invitation, 1984 April; 213038 (Box II:5, Folder 74)
    - Jean Cocteau -- Transportation, 1981 August-1982 October; 213037 (Box II:5, Folder 75)
    - Jean Cocteau -- Travel, FAF, 1981 March-September; 213036 (Box II:5, Folder 76)
    - Jean Cocteau -- Installation, 1984 May; 213035 (Box II:5, Folder 77)
    - Jean Cocteau -- Loans Pending, 1983 January-1984 February; 213034 (Box II:5, Folder 78)
    - Jean Cocteau -- Loans Confirmed, 1981 October-1984 April; 213033 (Box II:5, Folder 79)
    - Jean Cocteau -- Funding, 1980 August-1984 January; 213032 (Box II:5, Folder 80)
    - Jean Cocteau -- Project Budget, 1984 May 15-June 23; 213031 (Box II:5, Folder 81)
    - Cocteau -- US Loans, 1984 February-December; 213030 (Box II:5, Folder 82)
    - Cocteau -- Packing Lists and Diag., 1984 November-1985 February; 213029 (Box II:5, Folder 83)
    - Cocteau -- Foreign Loans, 1984 May; 213028 (Box II:5, Folder 84)
    - Jean Cocteau and the French (May 15-June 23, 1984), 1984 February-June; 213027 (Box II:5, Folder 85)
    - Jean Cocteau -- RRl File, 1982 July; 213026 (Box II:5, Folder 86)
    - L'Atelier Mourlot -- Estimated Budget, 1984 February-September; 213025 (Box II:5, Folder 87)
    - L'Atelier Mourlot -- Travel Vouchers, 1984 January-June; 213024 (Box II:5, Folder 88)
    - Boldini -- Photograph Orders, 1983 April-1984 March; 213023 (Box II:5, Folder 89)
    - Boldini -- Photo Bills, 1983 July-1984 September; 213022 (Box II:5, Folder 90)
    - Boldini -- Dispersal, 1984 December-1985 April; 213021 (Box II:5, Folder 91)
    - Boldini -- Ferrara, 1981 February-1984 October; 213020 (Box II:5, Folder 92)
    - Boldini -- Couriers, 1984 October-1985 January; 213019 (Box II:6, File 1)
    - Boldini -- Shipping, 1984 October-1985 May; 213018 (Box II:6, File 2)
    - Boldini -- Catalogue, 1984 November-1985 January; 213017 (Box II:6, File 3)
    - Boldini -- Correspondence, 1982 July-1984 November; 213016 (Box II:6, File 4)
    - Boldini -- Correspondence with Gary Reynolds, 1984 April 13-September 26; 213015 (Box II:6, File 5)
    - Boldini -- Project Budget, 1984; 213014 (Box II:6, File 6)
    - Boldini -- Lady Abdy Collection, 1982 July-1983 November; 213013 (Box II:6, File 7)
    - Boldini -- Valentin Abdy Collection, 1981 January-1983 October; 213012 (Box II:6, File 8)
    - Boldini -- Rothschild, 1980 April-1981 November; 213011 (Box II:6, File 9)
    - Boldini -- Megret Collection, 1981 January-October; 213010 (Box II:6, File 10)
    - Boldini -- 1983 NEA Grant, 1983 June-1984 February; 213009 (Box II:6, File 11)
    - Boldini -- Loans Confirmed (USA), 1982 July-1985 January; 213008 (Box II:6, File 12)
    - Boldini -- Loans Confirmed (Europe), 1983 February-1985 February; 213007 (Box II:6, File 13)
    - Boldini -- Loans Rejected, 1981 February-1984 June; 213006 (Box II:6, File 14)
    - Boldini -- Insurance, 1983 September-1985 February; 213005 (Box II:6, File 15)
    - Boldini -- Condition Reports and Loan Receipts, 1984 October-November; 213004 (Box II:6, File 16)
    - Boldini -- Exhibit (Nov. 13-Dec. 22, 1984), 1984 October; 213003 (Box II:6, File 17)
    - Boldini -- Social Segment (Portrait by Marcus Leatherdale), 1984 October-1985 January; 213002 (Box II:6, File 18)
    - Boldini -- Miscellaneous, 1984 August-1985 February; 213001 (Box II:6, File 19)
    - Small Gallery - Rene Santos "The Dog Show", 1985 January-February; 213000 (Box II:6, File 20)
    - Action/Precision -- Contract, 1984 May-December; 212999 (Box II:6, File 21)
    - Action/Precision -- Correspondence (1 of 2), 1984 May-1985 February; 212998 (Box II:6, File 22)
    - Action/Precision -- Corespondence (2 of 2), 1984 July-1985 February; 212997 (Box II:6, File 23)
    - Action/Precision -- Budget, Undated; 212996 (Box II:6, File 24)
    - Action/Precision -- Crate List, 1984 April-1985 March; 212995 (Box II:6, File 25)
    - Action/Precision -- Miscellaneous, 1983 September-1985 January; 212994 (Box II:6, File 26)
    - Precious -- Uptown Galleries Loans, 1985 February-June; 212993 (Box II:6, File 27)
    - Precious -- Mapplethorpe Studio Loan, 1985 February-May; 212992 (Box II:6, File 28)
    - Precious -- Private Lenders, 1985 February-May; 212991 (Box II:6, File 29)
    - Precious -- Soho Galleries Loans, 1985 February-May; 212990 (Box II:6, File 30)
    - Precious -- East Village Galleries Loans, 1984 November-1985 June; 212989 (Box II:6, File 31)
    - Precious -- Artist Loans, 1985 February-May; 212988 (Box II:6, File 32)
    - Precious -- Loan Forms and Correspondence, 1985 February-September; 212987 (Box II:6, File 33)
    - Precious -- Shipping and Insurance (1 of 2), 1985 February-May; 212986 (Box II:6, File 34)
    - Precious -- Shipping and Insurance, 1985 February-May; 212985 (Box II:6, File 35)
    - Precious -- Hand Delivered Works Checklist, 1985 March; 212984 (Box II:6, File 36)
    - Precious -- Dispersal, 1985 May; 212983 (Box II:6, File 37)
    - Precious -- Exhibition Expenses, 1985; 212982 (Box II:6, File 38)
    - Small Gallery -- Ruth Abrams, 1985 February-June; 212981 (Box II:6, File 39)
    - Small Gallery -- Early Pop Drawings, 1985 April-June; 212980 (Box II:6, File 40)
    - Small Gallery -- Early Pop Drawings, 1985 May-June; 212979 (Box II:6, File 41)
    - Labyrinth -- Loan Agreement, 1985 May-October; 212978 (Box II:6, File 42)
    - Labyrinth -- Installation and Shipping, 1985 April-July; 212977 (Box II:6, File 43)
    - Alfredo Jaar, 1985 June-September; 212976 (Box II:6, File 44)
    - Sol LeWitt -- Correspondence, 1985 May-August; 212975 (Box II:6, File 45)
    - Sol LeWitt -- Condition Report, 1985 June-July; 212974 (Box II:6, File 46)
    - Sol LeWitt -- Crate List, 1984 August-1985 June; 212973 (Box II:6, File 47)
    - Sol LeWitt -- Transportation, 1985 April-September; 212972 (Box II:6, File 48)
    - Indelible Image -- Correspondence, 1984 April-1986 May; 212971 (Box II:6, File 49)
    - Indelible Image -- Correspondence and Shipping, 1985 February-December; 212970 (Box II:6, File 50)
    - Indelible Image -- Grey Concoran Agreement, 1985 January-July; 212969 (Box II:6, File 51)
    - Indelible Image -- Symposium, 1985 August-1986 January; 212968 (Box II:6, File 52)
    - Josef Schutzenhofer Drawings - Small Gallery (War Photography), 1985 October-December; 212967 (Box II:6, File 53)
    - Contemporary Indian Art -- Condition Reports and Insurance (1 of 2), 1985 October-1986 June; 212966 (Box II:6, File 54)
    - Contemporary Indian Art -- Condition Report and Insurance (2 of 2), 1985-1986; 212965 (Box II:6, File 55)
    - Contemporary Indian Art -- Loan Agreement, Condition Reports, 1985-1986; 212964 (Box II:6, File 56)
    - Contemporary Indian Art -- Venue Correspondence, 1985 January-1986 March; 212963 (Box II:6, File 57)
    - Contemporary Indian Art -- Other Correspondence, 1984 December-1986 July; 212962 (Box II:6, File 58)
    - Contemporary Indian Art -- Indo-U.S. Subcommittee Correspondence and Expenses, 1984 August-1986 January; 212961 (Box II:6, File 59)
    - Modern Redux/ICI -- Loans Approved, 1986 January-June; 212960 (Box II:6, File 60)
    - Modern Redux/ICI -- Loans, 1986; 212959 (Box II:6, File 61)
    - Modern Redux/ICI -- Loans Rejected, 1986 April-June; 212958 (Box II:6, File 62)
    - Modern Redux -- Loan Forms and Letters, 1985 December-1986 February; 212957 (Box II:6, File 63)
    - Modern Redux -- Loan Forms for Credit Line, 1985-1986; 212956 (Box II:6, File 64)
    - Modern Redux -- Japanese Lenders, 1985 December-1986 September; 212955 (Box II:6, File 65)
    - Modern Redux -- New York Lenders, 1985 January-1986 April; 212954 (Box II:6, File 66)
    - Modern Redux -- European Lenders, 1985 December-1986 April; 212953 (Box II:6, File 67)
    - Modern Redux -- USA/Canada Lenders, 1985 December-1986 May; 212952 (Box II:6, File 68)
    - Modern Redux/ICI -- Problems, 1986 May-July; 212951 (Box II:6, File 69)
    - Modern Redux -- Symposia, 1986 March 31; 212950 (Box II:6, File 70)
    - Modern Redux/ICI -- Correspondence, 1987 August 7; 212949 (Box II:6, File 71)
    - Modern Redux -- Fundraising Letters, 1986 January 13; 212948 (Box II:6, File 72)
    - Modern Redux -- Brademas Reception, 1986 March-April; 212947 (Box II:7, File 1)
    - Modern Redux -- Architect. Leag. for Invitation, Undated; 212946 (Box II:7, File 2)
    - Modern Redux -- Shipping, 1986 January-September; 212945 (Box II:7, File 3)
    - Modern Redux -- Correspondence to Venues, 1985 August-December; 212944 (Box II:7, File 4)
    - Modern Redux -- Symposia, 1986 January-April; 212943 (Box II:7, File 5)
    - Modern Redux/ICI -- Correspondence, 1986 January-1987 May; 212942 (Box II:7, File 6)
    - Modern Redux -- Works Not Traveling and Dispersal, 1986 July-November; 212941 (Box II:7, File 7)
    - Modern Redux -- Donations to Exhibition (Correspondence and Thanks), 1986 March; 212940 (Box II:7, File 8)
    - Modern Redux -- ICI Tour, 1986 April-September; 212939 (Box II:7, File 9)
    - Modern Redux -- Post-Post Modern Architecture and Douglas Davis Miscellaneous (1 of 2), 1983 June-1986 January; 212938 (Box II:7, File 10)
    - Modern Redux -- Post-Post Modern Architecture and Douglas Davis Miscellaneous (2 of 2), 1985 August-2001 March; 212937 (Box II:7, File 11)
    - Modern Redux -- Miscellaneous, 1985 May-1986 April; 212936 (Box II:7, File 12)
    - Small Gallery -- Todd Siler Works of Art, 1986; 212935 (Box II:7, File 13)
    - Small Gallery -- Todd Siler Works of Art, 1986 January-May; 212934 (Box II:7, File 14)
    - Gallatin and His Circle -- Great Artists Fundraiser, Circa 1984-1986; 212933 (Box II:7, File 15)
    - Gallatin and His Circle Project, 1984 December-1985 August; 212932 (Box II:7, File 16)
    - A. E. Gallatin and His Circle -- Loans, Insurance and Condition, 1985 April-1986 July; 212931 (Box II:7, File 17)
    - Gallatin and His Circle -- Loans, 1986 February-May; 212930 (Box II:7, File 18)
    - Gallatin and His Circle -- Miscellaneous, 1985 November-1986 May; 212929 (Box II:7, File 19)
    - Robert Wilson -- Hamlet Machine (In Conjunction with Gallatin Exhibit), 1986 April-June; 212928 (Box II:7, File 20)
    - Robert Wilson (In Conjunction with Gallatin Exhibition), 1986 May-July; 212927 (Box II:7, File 21)
    - Abstract Appropriations (in Conjunction with Gallatin Exhibition), 1986 April-1987 December; 212926 (Box II:7, File 22)
    - Abstract Appropriations -- Loans, 1986 April-July; 212925 (Box II:7, File 23)
    - Rosalyn Drexler -- Correspondence, 1986 April-November; 212924 (Box II:7, File 24)
    - Rosalyn Drexier -- Loans, 1986 April-1987 February; 212923 (Box II:7, File 25)
    - Rosalyn Drexler -- Intimate Emotions (Greenville County, Sept. 9-Oct. 12, 1986), 1986 September; 212922 (Box II:7, File 26)
    - Rosalyn Drexler -- Intimate Emotions (Greenville County, Sept. 9-Oct 12, 1986), 1986 August-December; 212921 (Box II:7, File 27)
    - Rosalyn Drexler -- intimate Emotions (University of Iowa, Nov. 1-Jan. 11, 1987), 1986 June-1987 March; 212920 (Box II:7, File 28)
    - Rosalyn Drexler -- Miscellaneous, 1986 June-1987 August; 212919 (Box II:7, File 29)
    - Drexler and Abrams -- Shipping, 1986 May-September; 212918 (Box II:7, File 30)
    - Rosalyn Drexler -- Condition Report Book, 1986-1987; 212917 (Box II:7, File 31)
    - Ruth Abrams -- Loans (July 10-August 28, 1989), 1986 May-September; 212916 (Box II:7, File 32)
    - Ruth Abrams -- Paintings 1940-1985 (Condition Reports), Circa 1985-1986; 212915 (Box II:7, File 33)
    - Ruth Abrams -- Expenses, 1985 September-1986 July; 212914 (Box II:7, File 34)
    - Ruth Abrams -- A Retrospective, 1986 March-August; 212913 (Box II:7, File 35)
    - Arnulf Rainer -- Correspondence, 1985 September-1987 August; 212912 (Box II:7, File 36)
    - Arnulf Rainer -- Cross Paintings, 1986 June-October; 212911 (Box II:7, File 37)
    - Arnulf rainer -- Cross Paintings, 1986 July-October; 212910 (Box II:7, File 38)
    - Arnulf Rainer -- Florida Atlantic University, 1985 October 25; 212909 (Box II:7, File 39)
    - Simon Linke -- Paintings (Small Gallery in Conj. with Rainer), 1986 July-November; 212908 (Box II:7, File 40)
    - William Brice -- Correspondence, 1986 February-1987 January; 212907 (Box II:7, File 41)
    - William Brice -- Correspondence, 1986 January-July; 212906 (Box II:7, File 42)